Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Master Wei is quite cunning.
المعلم وي ماكر جدًا.
He's being so guarded against us.
إنه حذر للغاية ضدنا.
It's hard for us to find a breakthrough.
من الصعب علينا أن نجد اختراقًا.
Truly quite crafty.
ماكرة حقا.
To think he chose such a place.
أعتقد أنه اختار مثل هذا المكان.
I took a quick look the other day.
لقد ألقيت نظرة سريعة في اليوم الآخر.
There are many rooms there.
هناك العديد من الغرف هناك.
It would be difficult to pinpoint his exact location.
سيكون من الصعب تحديد موقعه بالضبط.
So what should we do?
إذن ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل؟
Let's investigate again tonight.
دعونا نحقق مرة أخرى الليلة.
I'll go back and prepare.
سأعود وأستعد.
No need.
لا حاجة.
Too many people would be inconvenient.
سيكون وجود عدد كبير جدًا من الأشخاص أمرًا غير مريح.
Just the two of us will go.
سوف نذهب نحن الاثنين فقط.
We'll inform you immediately if anything comes up.
سوف نقوم بإعلامك على الفور إذا حدث أي شيء.
Master, we've brought her.
سيدي، لقد أحضرناها.
Understood.
مفهومة.
You may leave.
يمكنك المغادرة.
Xiao Qing, you're here.
شياو تشينغ، أنت هنا.
Master.
يتقن.
You must be thirsty.
لابد أنك عطشان.
Here.
هنا.
For your filial devotion,
من أجل إخلاصك الأبوي،
today I made an exception to consult the Serpent Immortal.
اليوم قمت باستثناء استشارة الثعبان الخالد.
The Serpent Immortal agreed to grant me power
وافق الثعبان الخالد على منحي القوة
to save your mother.
لإنقاذ والدتك.
However,
لكن،
please rest assured, Serpent Immortal and Master,
يرجى الاطمئنان، أيها الثعبان الخالد والسيد،
as long as I can save my mother,
طالما أستطيع إنقاذ أمي،
I'm willing to do anything.
أنا مستعد لفعل أي شيء.
Look over there, quick!
أنظر هناك، بسرعة!
I heard the Serpent Immortal will manifest tomorrow.
سمعت أن الثعبان الخالد سوف يظهر غدًا.
Master Wei will perform miracles to help the suffering again.
سوف يقوم المعلم وي بعمل المعجزات لمساعدة المصابين مرة أخرى.
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك
snake worship in mythology has a long history.
عبادة الثعابين في الأساطير لها تاريخ طويل.
Like Nuwa and Fuxi,
مثل نيو وفوكسي،
they were deities with human heads and snake bodies.
كانوا آلهة برؤوس بشرية وأجساد ثعبانية.
Therefore snakes
لذلك الثعابين
are often considered incarnations of dragons.
تعتبر في كثير من الأحيان تجسيدات للتنين.
In our...
في...
In our Northeast region,
في منطقتنا الشمالية الشرقية،
these immortals are supposed to help people.
من المفترض أن هؤلاء الخالدين يساعدون الناس.
How do they use this to deceive people?
كيف يستخدمون هذا لخداع الناس؟
These frauds
هذه الاحتيالات
prey on people's worship of immortals.
استغلال عبادة الناس للخالدين.
When the immortal speaks,
عندما يتكلم الخالد،
if you don't obey and something happens, who's to blame?
إذا لم تطع وحدث شيء فمن هو الملام؟
Right?
يمين؟
Better to believe it exists, just in case.
من الأفضل أن نصدق أنه موجود، فقط في حالة.
That makes sense.
هذا منطقي.
Human life is predestined by heaven.
الحياة البشرية مقدرة من السماء.
To go against heaven's will
للذهاب ضد إرادة السماء
would invite disaster.
من شأنه أن يؤدي إلى الكارثة.
Are you certain you want to save your mother
هل أنت متأكد أنك تريد إنقاذ والدتك؟
by sacrificing your lifespan?
من خلال التضحية بعمرك؟
I only ask that my mother's illness be cured.
كل ما أطلبه هو شفاء مرض والدتي.
Once this arrow is loosed, it cannot be retrieved.
بمجرد إطلاق هذا السهم، لن يكون من الممكن استرجاعه.
Think carefully.
فكر جيدا.
I've thought it through.
لقد فكرت في الأمر جيدًا.
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
This cup seems to have been tampered with.
يبدو أن هذا الكأس قد تم العبث به.
There's a strange smell.
هناك رائحة غريبة.
Knockout Potion.
جرعة الضربة القاضية.
Who's it meant to knock out?
من هو المقصود بالضربة القاضية؟
Me.
أنا.
Auspicious day and hour,
يوم وساعة مباركة
golden boys and jade girls hold my towel,
الأولاد الذهبيون والفتيات اليشم يمسكون بمنشفتي،
mystical platform and purple canopy crown my body,
منصة غامضة ومظلة أرجوانية تتوج جسدي،
granting me eternal life.
منحني الحياة الأبدية.
Dawn is coming, let's go first.
الفجر قادم، فلنذهب أولاً.
Go.
يذهب.
Officer Gu.
الضابط جو.
You've come at the right time.
لقد أتيت في الوقت المناسب.
I was about to send someone to the Bai residence for you.
لقد كنت على وشك إرسال شخص ما إلى مقر باي من أجلك.
Any new discoveries?
هل هناك أي اكتشافات جديدة؟
Not a discovery,
ليس اكتشافا
but a murder case.
بل قضية قتل.
The night watchman reported it this morning.
وأفاد حارس الليل بذلك صباح اليوم.
A body was found in the western suburbs.
تم العثور على جثة في الضاحية الغربية.
The deceased is Yao Qing, twenty years old.
المتوفى هو ياو تشينغ، يبلغ من العمر عشرين عامًا.
Suspected snake venom poisoning.
الاشتباه في التسمم بسم الثعبان.
Time of death was last night.
وقت الوفاة كان الليلة الماضية.
This girl isn't...
هذه الفتاة ليست...
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Master Wei of Eternal Spirit Hall.
المعلم وي من قاعة الروح الأبدية.
Seems related to the Serpent Immortal again.
يبدو أنه مرتبط بالثعبان الخالد مرة أخرى.
Serpent Immortal.
الثعبان الخالد.
Let me ask her what happened.
دعني أسألها ماذا حدث؟
A snake wouldn't bite the same spot so many times.
لن يعض الثعبان نفس المكان عدة مرات.
How could it?
كيف يمكن ذلك؟
The wounds are too uniform.
الجروح موحدة للغاية.
A snake's body is covered in scales.
جسم الثعبان مغطى بالقشور.
The blood and flesh under her nails
الدم واللحم تحت أظافرها
couldn't be from a snake.
لا يمكن أن يكون من ثعبان.
She was murdered.
لقد تم قتلها.
But was it really Master Wei?
ولكن هل كان هذا حقا السيد وي؟
So, what did you find?
إذن ماذا وجدت؟
They did this to her.
لقد فعلوا بها هذا.
Thinking they could deceive the world.
ظنوا أنهم قادرون على خداع العالم.
Committing crimes in the Serpent Immortal's name.
ارتكاب الجرائم باسم الثعبان الخالد.
They're acting too brazenly.
إنهم يتصرفون بوقاحة شديدة.
Was it really Master Wei?
هل كان حقا السيد وي؟
I'm not sure about that.
أنا لست متأكدة من ذلك.
But what I am sure of is...
ولكن ما أنا متأكد منه هو...
Her wounds were man-made.
جروحها كانت من صنع الإنسان.
The purpose was...
وكان الهدف...
To make us think it was the Serpent Immortal's revenge.
لتجعلنا نعتقد أنها كانت انتقام الثعبان الخالد.
Master Wei has great prestige around here.
السيد وي يتمتع بمكانة عظيمة هنا.
If he's behind this...
إذا كان هو وراء هذا...
Then it's complicated.
ثم الأمر معقد.
Yao Qing definitely wasn't the first.
بالتأكيد لم يكن ياو تشينغ الأول.
Stay out of this matter.
ابقى خارج هذا الموضوع .
I'll investigate.
سأحقق في الأمر.
No.
لا.
They're too cunning.
إنهم ماكرون للغاية.
If we want to expose them...
إذا أردنا أن نفضحهم...
Rushing in won't work.
التسرع لن يجدي نفعا.
Here's a better idea.
وهنا فكرة أفضل.
Since they already think...
لأنهم يفكرون بالفعل...
we're his followers...
نحن أتباعه...
I need you to help me put on an act.
أريد منك أن تساعدني في تمثيل هذا الفعل.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I'll fully cooperate.
سأتعاون بشكل كامل.
Forget grievances, forget sorrows, soul returns to darkness.
انسى المظالم، انسى الأحزان، تعود الروح إلى الظلام.
May your journey be smooth.
أتمنى أن تكون رحلتك سلسة.
Heaven and earth bear witness, no spirits shall disturb.
السماء والأرض تشهدان، لا ينبغي لأي روح أن يزعج.
May you dream into the great void.
أتمنى أن تحلم بالفراغ العظيم.
Master.
يتقن.
This month's...
هذا الشهر...
Please accept it.
من فضلك تقبل ذلك.
There's something.
هناك شيئا ما.
This...
هذا...
Recently someone came for treatment...
لقد جاء شخص ما مؤخرًا للعلاج ...
but I suspect he's not actually ill.
لكني أظن أنه ليس مريضًا فعليًا.
And he noticed...
ولاحظ...
this tattoo on my arm.
هذا الوشم على ذراعي.
How old?
كم عمره؟
Early twenties.
أوائل العشرينات.
Handsome with piercing eyes.
وسيم ذو عيون ثاقبة.
With two women accompanying him.
برفقته امرأتين.
Take me to see him.
خذني لرؤيته.
Master Wei.
المعلم وي.
Where's Master Wei?
أين السيد وي؟
Just a moment.
لحظة واحدة.
Master Wei will be here shortly.
السيد وي سيكون هنا قريبا.
That's them.
هؤلاء هم.
The young man's back again, good.
لقد عاد الشاب مرة أخرى، جيد.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Master Wei is coming.
السيد وي قادم.
All problems will be solved.
سيتم حل جميع المشاكل.
Good.
جيد.
Kill him.
اقتله
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
He won't survive the night.
لن ينجو من الليل.
Don't rush.
لا تستعجل.
Master Wei will be here soon.
السيد وي سيكون هنا قريبا.
Master Wei.
المعلم وي.
Master Wei, please help save him!
سيد وي، من فضلك ساعد في إنقاذه!
We're truly sincere this time.
لقد كنا صادقين حقا هذه المرة.
Let's not talk about money now.
دعونا لا نتحدث عن المال الآن.
This...
هذا...
What's wrong with your husband?
ماذا حدث لزوجك؟
Sister...
أخت...
You tell him.
أنت تخبره.
My brother...
أخي...
Is impotent.
عاجز.
So he and his wife...
فهو وزوجته...
Have never had children.
لم يكن لدي أطفال أبدًا.
It's alright.
لا بأس.
Let me examine him first.
دعني أفحصه أولاً.
Great Serpent Immortal, comfort this form.
أيها الثعبان العظيم الخالد، عزي هذا الشكل.
Disciple's spirit, guard its true form.
روح التلميذ، احرس شكلها الحقيقي.
Five organ deities, each maintain peace.
خمسة آلهة أعضاء، كل واحد منهم يحافظ على السلام.
H-how is it?
ح-كيف الحال؟
Your brother's condition developed over time.
لقد تطورت حالة أخيك مع مرور الوقت.
It can't be cured immediately.
لا يمكن علاجه على الفور.
This...
هذا...
Is there any other way?
هل هناك أي طريقة أخرى؟
Money is no object.
المال ليس مشكلة.
You two...
انتما الاثنان...
Let's talk privately.
دعونا نتحدث على انفراد.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Young man.
شاب.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
Have some water first.
اشرب بعض الماء أولاً.
Wait a moment.
انتظر لحظة.
To cure human ailments
لعلاج الأمراض البشرية
one must absorb yin energy as catalyst
يجب على المرء أن يمتص طاقة الين كمحفز
connect heaven and earth's meridians
ربط خطوط الطول في السماء والأرض
and relieve the body's afflictions
وتخفيف آلام الجسم
This is Healing through Yin
هذا هو الشفاء من خلال الين
a life-saving method
طريقة لإنقاذ الحياة
not a source of calamity
ليس مصدرًا للكوارث
To request medicine from Serpent Immortal
لطلب الدواء من الثعبان الخالد
one must offer yin energy
يجب تقديم طاقة الين
You two
انتما الاثنان
are you prepared?
هل انت مستعد؟
If not for your meddling
إن لم يكن لتدخلك
this matter
هذه المسألة
wouldn't have fallen to you
لم يكن ليقع عليك
Now let me enjoy myself first
الآن دعني أستمتع بنفسي أولاً